<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Love for Girlfriend</string>
    <string name="app_concept">Love Letters</string>
    <string name="more">More App</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="copy">Letter Copy</string>
    <string name="Inter_adUnitId">ca-app-pub-5906384591064336/9740197951</string>
    <string name="Banner_adUnitId">ca-app-pub-5906384591064336/9629066051</string>
    <string name="letter1">Sweetie, I can still clearly recall the day I first met you. You entered my life on that day, and everything changed for the better. Since then, you have showered me with love and positivity, and I have grown to be a contented man. I wish that you always stay close to me and keep making me feel lucky every day.</string>
    <string name="letter2">I keep falling in love with you because of something about you that is so amazing. I may not have told you, but I want to tell you that you have given my life a purpose and a direction that was missing until you came into my life. It is difficult to imagine my life without you because you are the one who rules it. I LOVE YOU</string>
    <string name="letter3">Darling, Falling in love with you has been the best thing for me in this life. I still wonder how such a beautiful, loving, and caring girl can love someone like me. I think I have just been lucky. I promise to always be there for you, to keep you happy and smiling.</string>
    <string name="letter4">Sometimes, words are not enough to express the best feelings. I want you to know that you are like a dream come true to me, and with you in my arms, I feel so complete and happy. Thank you for choosing and loving me beyond conditions.</string>
    <string name="letter5">Whenever I see you smile, it makes me a happy man. Whenever I hold you in my arms, I feel I am holding my world. Whenever I am with you, every moment feels extra special. \nI am blessed to have a girlfriend like you who loves me, cares for me, and makes me the most fortunate person in this world.</string>
    <string name="letter6">Honey, I have found the love of my life and my best friend in you. The way you understand me, support me, love me, and care for me is beyond words. I thank the Almighty for sending an angel like you in my life who filled my heart happiness and love.</string>
    <string name="letter7">Sweetie, I was so alone in this whole wide world, but I found a companion for life in you when you arrived. You have changed my life, and you have made me a happy and blessed person.</string>
    <string name="letter8">Love, You may not know, but you are the only one who will rule my heart. No matter how old I get, my love will grow with each passing day. Love you to the moon and back</string>
    <string name="letter9">Honey, When you are with me, smiles and joy are surrounding me. When you are with me, flowers are blooming everywhere. I am so blessed that I have you as the love of my life. Miss you</string>
    <string name="letter10">Dearest darling, I still remember that beautiful day when you accepted my proposal to be my girlfriend. Since that day, my life has only been good and cheerful with you. Love you, my dear.</string>
    <string name="letter11">Dear Name, I sometimes wonder if I was living a life when you were not with me because after you have arrived, you have made my life so full of love, care, and affection. You truly have made me a lucky man.</string>
    <string name="letter12">Love, I want to promise you that there will be no day of your life when you will not find me by your side. There will be no day when I will not be loving you and pampering you because you mean the world to me.</string>
    <string name="letter13">It is the power of your love that has changed me for good. All the happiness and success that I enjoy today, is all because of the love you have showered me with.</string>
    <string name="letter14">Honey, This life is so short, and I would not want to waste even a moment of it by not loving you. I want to fill your life with so much love and affection that there is no place for any sorrows. I promise to love you unconditionally forever.</string>
    <string name="letter15">Dearest darling, My heart only beats for you, and my eyes always look for you. You are the most special person who completes me in every sense. I am always going to love you more than anyone else, and I will always be by your side because we are meant to be together till eternity. I Love you</string>
    <string name="letter16">Sunshine, Falling in love with you has been the most beautiful accident of my life, and I will always be thankful that it happened. You opened an entirely new world where I felt alive and adored. Had you not been there with me, I would have been a lost soul who has no idea what I was missing. Love you and miss you</string>
    <string name="letter17">My love, I wish I could start my day with a warm hug from you because you are my lucky charm. And I wish I could end my nights with your smile because you are the source of all my strength. Having you around me makes me feel so much stronger and happier that I cannot put in words. Come back soon.</string>
    <string name="letter18">Dear, My life would have been so different had you not been there with me. You have filled every corner of my heart with your love. You have showered me with so much care and affection that I feel I must have done something right in my life to deserve you. Love you forever, my darling.</string>
    <string name="letter19">Sweetie, Every moment that I spend with you becomes a beautiful memory of my life. My feelings for you multiply with each passing day and my heart always skips a beat when you look at me with a smile on your face. You are the love of my life, and I am truly blessed to have you.</string>
    <string name="letter20">When you hold my hand, when you kiss me, when you hug me…. I feel I am the most fortunate person in this world. There is something so magical about the love we both have for each other because it brings me immense joy. I am glad that our paths crossed and we fell in love. Thanks for choosing me</string>
    <string name="letter21">Dearest love, When I am with you, I wish that time passes slowly, because I want to make the most of every moment I live with you. You are the most special present from the Almighty, and I am fortunate that you are mine. I promise to love you till eternity.</string>
    <string name="letter22"> Love you forever, my love. When you walk hand in hand with me, I feel the strongest and the happiest man in this world. When you look into my eyes, I feel that I can conquer this world. Thank you for always believing in me and bringing out the best in me.</string>
    <string name="letter23">Every time you look at me, the sparkles in your eyes steal my heart. Whenever you kiss me, you win me over. When you hug me, you melt me with your love. Sometimes, I feel that you are some gorgeous magician who always casts her spell on me.</string>
    <string name="letter24">Honey, Seeing you smile always brings me joy. Hearing you talk is like music to my ears. Hugging you tight makes me feel I am alive. I am blessed to have someone as loving, as caring as you by my side. I know that life will always be blessed and cheerful when you are with me. You make this world beautiful for me, and the way you make me feel can never be expressed in words. I will always love you, and I promise that you will find strength and happiness in our relationship.</string>
    <string name="letter25">My adorable darling, Until I met you, I had no idea that life could be full of happiness. There are so many new things and feelings that I have experienced with you. You brought into my life so much warmth and love that I have learned to live a life beyond my insecurities. You have become my biggest strength and my most precious asset. I will love you till my last breath, and I will always stand by you till eternity.</string>
    <string name="letter26">My dear, Having your hand in mine is the only thing I had ever wanted, and now that I have you as a part of my life, I have nothing more to ask for. May you keep walking with me in this journey, and may we both experience many new things together in this life. Looking forward to a joyful and adventurous life with you, my love.</string>
    <string name="letter27">Honey, When you are by my side, I am on top of this world. When you are holding my hand, I know that I can achieve the impossible because you are there to believe in me. I have no words to thank you, but I want to tell you that you will always have my heart with you, and I will always keep loving you.</string>
    <string name="letter28">When I first met you, I had no idea that we would have a future together, but I am glad that we transformed from strangers to lovers. You are the most beautiful and loving person I know, and I feel fortunate that you are mine. I hope our love grows with each passing day, and we always stay happy together.</string>
    <string name="letter29">Love, You are the rainbow of my life that has filled my heart with beautiful colors of love. Every day, I thank God for sending you in my life and blessing me with the joys that I was missing in life. I may have never expressed it, but I want you to know that you mean the world to me. No matter how things will change with time, my love is always going to stay the same for me. Love you forever and ever. Your true love.</string>
    <string name="letter30">Dearest darling, There is nothing I want more from this life because I have got you. The only wish I have is that I always have you with me in each moment, sharing all my joys and sorrows. May each day of this life, I start my day with your smile and end it with your warmth and love. I pray that our bond of love is always blessed and we stay together forever and ever.</string>
    <string name="letter31">Sweetie, I always wondered if true love existed, but then I found you, and I found answers to all my questions. It was so easy to love you, to pamper you, to be there with you. Thank you for teaching me to love and be loved and make this life a fairytale. I wish we always stay together and celebrate our relationship with the same energies and sparkles as we do today.</string>
    <string name="letter32"> Love, I love you so much that you are always in my thoughts, no matter what I am doing. I always think about the beautiful memories we have created together, and I want to make many more lovely moments. You are the best thing that has happened to me, and I thank you for all the love you have brought into my life. Thank you for making me a fortunate man.</string>
    <string name="letter33">Hon, It was never easy to find true love in life, but I am fortunate to find you. You walked into my life and transformed it with your unconditional love. It is the power of your love that I am wearing smiles every day, and I am making all my dreams come true.You are so special that you make me fall in love with you every day and empower me with all the strength to conquer this world. Love You..</string>
    <string name="letter34">Love, I was convinced that love is blind because someone as gorgeous as you fell in love with someone like me. But whatever be the case, I feel that I am truly fortunate that you have accepted my love. Thank you</string>
    <string name="letter35">Honey, I want to look into your eyes when we walk together, but I am scared to tumble. I want you by my side, but then I might not be able to look at your face. Therefore, I choose to sit down and enjoy this life with you, looking into your eyes and kissing you without any distractions.</string>
    <string name="letter36">Darling, I want to tell you that you are my first thought in the morning and my last thought before I fall asleep. No minute passes by when I do not sigh, wanting to be near you, with you. I know you are out there chasing your dreams, and I am here trying to make a life of my own. However, I cannot help missing you badly. You are a part of everything I do because I hold you close to my heart.</string>
    <string name="letter37">My Dearest Love Today, I was at the supermarket when a couple in front of me stood holding hands. I immediately thought of you and the warmth you shared with me whenever it got chilly during the winter months. The packet of ramen on the shelf reminded me of the annoying slurping sound you make while eating. I almost bought a beer box when I realized that the one who drinks it all isn’t waiting at home. Everything around me reminds me of you. No matter where I look or what I do, you are always with me. I miss you every moment of every single day.</string>
    <string name="letter38">Dear (Nickname) Waking up alone is the worst thing ever. I feel as though the days without you have been stretching so long. It’s almost unbearable. But know this, my love, I am proud of what you are doing, and you always have my full support. I miss you like crazy, but I find solace because you are happy doing what you love doing the most. You are where you always wanted to be, and I am truly happy for you. All I wish for is to meet you soon to make up for all the time we missed being together. I hope to see you soon!</string>
    <string name="letter39">Hi Honey, Even though we are miles away from each other, I feel the deep bond we share each time I think of you. I miss your wet kisses and warm hugs. I miss the way you act funny, just to make me laugh. I miss the way we talk about anything and everything under the sun. And I miss the way you bite your upper lip when you are up to some mischief. But I know we both have to be strong if we want to make our dreams come true. And I hope we’ll soon be together, never to be separated again. Love you, my darling.</string>
    <string name="letter40">Hi Babe, If absence makes the heart grow fonder, then I think I hold all the ‘fondness’ in the world for you. Each day spent without you feels like years. I know we promised to stay strong, but sometimes I cannot help wishing you were here to hold me and tell me that everything will be alright. Watching Netflix alone is no fun, and even my favorite fried chicken feels tasteless without you. I miss you from the bottom of my heart and yearn for the day I’d see you again.</string>
    <string name="letter41">Dear (Nickname) It has been exactly 286 days, 13 hours, and 15 minutes since you left the city, which means I have to brave it out another 250 days till I can finally have you in my arms. Whenever I miss you, I hug your Lakers’ jersey and try to sleep, hoping to see you in my dreams. I hope you are happy in your new place. Do not worry about me, as your love is enough for me to get through these days of physical separation. Though I miss you terribly, I want you to know that I am there with you and would like you to come back to me only after you have completed the task you set out to achieve. All the best, my dear. See you soon.</string>
    <string name="letter42">Hey (Nickname) You are my sun and my moon that light up my world. You are the ketchup to my fries and the guacamole to my nachos. You are the Noah to my Allie and Harry to my Sally. You are the William to my Kate. You are the iOS to my Apple and Windows to my Dell. You are the tint to my lipstick and glimmer to my gloss. You are my everything. Love you lots!</string>
    <string name="letter43">Dear (Name) We bicker and fight when we are together, and now that you are away, I feel so lonely without you. I now realize how much I love you. I remember how you’d start laughing in the middle of a fight or buy me ice cream to make up with me or hug me in bed to tell me you still love me. Your gentle touch, your sweet voice, and your sweet scent still linger on and keep me going. I wish I could make you come back sooner. I love you, baby. I always will.</string>
    <string name="letter44">My Dear, I hope you are well. I’m writing to you to tell you that I pledge my heart to you. I promise to give this relationship my all and make it work despite the distance. I think of you each day, my love. I now see how incomplete my life feels without you, and I’m glad that our time apart has cleared my mind of any doubts. I want you to know that I wish the best for you no matter where you are. I hope to meet you and hug you soon. Love</string>
    <string name="letter45">Dear (Name) I have never been able to say this when you were here, but this distance between us has pushed me to pour my heart to you. I want you to know that despite being surrounded by loneliness, the only thing that keeps me sane is your love. It is very easy to feel bogged down by adversities, but I keep afloat because your love consumes my entirety. With you, in my life, there is nothing that I cannot overcome. You bring so much positivity in my life that negativity does not even look in my direction. I never said this before but know that you are the love of my life, and I hope to spend an eternity with you.</string>
    <string name="letter46">My Love, All my worries seemed insignificant from the time I fell in love with you. It feels like your love is the ultimate solution to everything. When I’m happy, I think of you. When I’m lonely, I think of you. Even when I’m angry, I think of you, and everything seems to dissipate as your love takes over. I feel I’m the luckiest girl in the world to have a wonderful man like you in my life. You are the most amazing person I know, and my strength to face this distance comes from you. I cannot wait to drown you in my love. See you soon.</string>
    <string name="letter47">Sweetheart, You will be happy to know I fixed the garage shelf today. I know I should not be bragging about it, but I feel like an achiever. Well, thanks to you, you have transformed me, and I love this version of myself. Falling in love with you has made me see my true self. And I wish for nothing but the best for you. Continue working hard, and one day, all your dreams will come true. You deserve all the happiness in the world, and I hope I can make you happy too. And no matter where you are, remember that I will always love you.</string>
    <string name="letter48">Honey Here’s another letter to remind you that I love you and I am thinking about you. I love the way you look at me; it makes me feel beautiful and precious. I love the way you kiss me. I love your geeky nature; it assures me that you will always have a solution to all my silly problems. I love your handsome face; it makes my heart race. And finally, I love you making me feel special every day, every second. You are the most special person in my life, and I can never stop loving you. Love you loads.</string>
    <string name="letter49">Dear (Nickname) I wish you could feel my heartbeat whenever you smile. I wish you could see the twinkle in my eyes whenever you are around. I wish you could sense my skin tingle under your warm touch. I wish you could feel my love for you despite this distance between us. Yes, I love you more than you can imagine, and I know we are just meant to be. I love you</string>
    <string name="letter50">Love , When I think about us, I wonder if we can keep going, with this distance between us. I then remember the wonderful times we spent together, and I cannot be more sure that we are simply perfect together. You may annoy me by blowing air bubbles in your glass like a little kid, but you also put me to sleep on days when I am feeling down. You never remember to take out the trash, but you always get my favorite cake for my birthday. There is absolutely no doubt that I love you. I love you and accept you with your flaws and strengths. Hugs and kisses</string>
</resources>